A Guide to the Postcard Photographs of U.S. & British Writers 1800-1900
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Postcard Photographs Depicting U.S. & British Writers 1800-1900
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7267-a
Eighteen items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of eighteen items, 19th and 20th century postcard photographs of fifteen American literary figures and three British writers.
Contents List
- Arnold, Matthew 1800-1900
- Burroughs, William 1800-1900
- Cather, Willa 1800-1900
- Darwin, Charles 1800-1900
- Doolittle, Hilda (H.D.) 1800-1900
- Faulkner, William 1800-1900
- Hemingway, Ernest 1800-1900
- James, Henry 1800-1900
- Lowell, Amy 1800-1900
- McCullers, Carson 1800-1900
- Melville, Herman 1800-1900
- Miller, Henry/Durrell, Lawrence 1800-1900
- Poe, Edgar Allen 1800-1900
- Pound, Ezra 1800-1900
- Sarton, May 1800-1900
- Twain, Mark 1800-1900
- Whitman, Walt 1800-1900